

Syed Waris Babar

Administrator at Sunrise Academy

A diversified and target driven professional with 3 years experience in Administration and Education industry, covering the fields of Budgeting, Operations, Customer Service, Administration and Analysis & Reporting. Responsible for designing and monitoring information system for better visibility and decision making, influences and recommends directions to help shape new business development, administrative structure strategy based. Attract clients by directing business strategies, promoting business / organiztion nationally and directing staff.

Contact Info

□03214885221

₩ waris9100@gmail.com

♠ House # 3 Street # 2 Ghaziabad, Lahore. Lahore, Pakistan

Strengths & Skills

- ✓ Administrative Skills
- ✓ Counseling
- Microsoft Office

- ✓ Communication Skills
- ✓ Documentation
- MS Excel

- ✓ Computer Skills
- ✓ English
- MS Word

Academics

Title	Institute	Score	Date
MBA	University of Sargodha, Lahore	3.5 CGPA	2018
B.Com	The Superior College, Lahore	60%	2015
I.Com	Govt. Islamia college, Lahore	75%	2013
Matriculation	Takbeer Model High School, Lahore	60%	2011



Title Authority Date

Computer Foundation Institute of professional and computer Starting March 2019

technology.

Experience 3 years

CompanyDesignationDurationArqamhouse Public Boys High SchoolTeacherDec 2018 - Present1 yearNECS School SystemTeacherAug 2017 - Aug 20181 yearSunrise AcademyOffice Administrator / Office CoordinatorOct 2015 - Present4.2 years

Work History

Arqamhouse Public Boys High School Dec 2018 - Present (1 year)

Teacher Lahore, Pakistan

I am currently working in Arqamhouse Public Boys High School as an Computer Teacher dealing with the students at matriculation level. I have got best teacher award from this school and an appriciaiton award from the Principal.

NECS School System Aug 2017 - Aug 2018 (1 year)

Teacher Lahore., Pakistan

I worked as an Computer teacher at NECS School System.

Sunrise Academy Oct 2015 - Present (4.2 years)

Office Administrator / Office Coordinator

Lahore, Pakistan

Currentlty working as Administrator in Sunrise Academy. Providing queries to the visitors, handling student affairs, dealing with teachers, collection of fee, arranging meetings, accounts maintenance and correpondence with the higher authories. Responsible for all administrative matters of Academy.





Promotion Coordinator Feb 2014 - May 2014 (3 months)

Company: NEO TV / Ch. Abdul Rehman

www.neonetwork.pk

Tools: Social Media, Personal Relations, Stalls etc.

I, and my team worked for the promotion on NEO TV Channel. We have used social media, personal relations for the promotion and at the time of opening/innaugration we have arranged different events in differebnt parks accross the city i.e Lahore.

Awards

Title	Authority	Date
Best Teacher	Arqamhouse Pubic Boys High School	2019
Best Employee	Sunrise Academy	2018



Ammad Arshad | 0324-8004444

Imperial College of Business Studies ammad.arshad@imperial.edu.pk

Industries

• Education/Training

Languages

- Punjabi Native
- Urdu Native
- English Medium

* Functional Areas

- Administration And Office Support
- Teachers/Education, Training & Development

☆ Hobbies

- Reading Books
- Teaching
- Writing Articles
- Creating Designs
- Playing Cricket